business-software.com 2019-09-15

# Privacy Statement

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the website, www.Business-Software.com, and its various related services (together referred to as the “Site”). Gate58 Marketing, LLC (referred to as “we”, “us”, or the “Company”), the provider of the Site, is committed to respecting your privacy rights.   This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of the Site’s Terms of Use (referred to as “Terms”), and by accessing or using the Site, you agree to be bound by all of its Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, please do not access or use this Site.

**1\. What information do we collect from you?**

In order to provide you with various services on our Site, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that allows us to know who you are. When you engage in an activity or request for Site content on our site, such as, for example, downloading a Top 10 Reports, white paper, or software demo, or accepting a promotional offer from our Site, we will ask you to either simply submit your corporate email or a more detailed online registration form.  It is completely optional to you to engage in these activities. If you choose to engage in a particular activity on our Site, we will ask that you provide limited personal information related to your company which includes your first and last name, address, email, telephone number, name and size of your company, job title, country and information about your interest in the particular products/services of your preference. If you do not wish to provide us with your personal identifiable information, you may not be able to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our Site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site’s Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. An URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (“TCP/IP”) network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet. Even if you don’t register at our Site, we will still collect your Non-Personally Identifiable Information upon your visit to our Site.

**2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?**

We collect Personally Identifiable Information about you when you voluntarily provide us with your Personally Identifiable Information to register on our Site by giving us your consent from checking the box acknowledging that you have read this Privacy Policy and also the Terms of Use.  And by consenting, you are giving us the rights to use your Personally Identifiable Information explained in our Policy and Terms.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve product and service offerings, and customize the Site’s content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Site Terms of Use and this Private Policy.

In addition, we may also collect, or our third party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. This information is ultimately stored in the form of store categories, and, in some cases, specific URLs. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our site and to gather demographic information. Our third party ad servers may also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our site.

**3\. With whom do we share your information?**

When you choose to register at our Site by providing your Personally Identifiable Information, you are giving us your express consent to share your Personal Identifiable Information with our affiliates and third-party vendors for marketing and promotional purposes of their products or services. The use of your Personally Identifiable Information may result in follow-up communications from third-party partners or vendors about their products or services related to your selected activity or requested Site content.  For example, after you registered to download a Top 10 Report or provided us with your corporate email address in exchange for one of our “Top” Reports with a free gift offer, we may transfer your Personal Identifiable Information to those third-party vendors with products or services related to your selected or offered activity and those vendors may contact you to provide additional information about their products or services; or, if you download to test or view a vendor demo, the third-party vendor featured on that demo may contact you to provide additional information about its product or service. 

When your Personal Identifiable Information is forwarded to those third-party partners or vendors, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by those third-party partners or vendors is governed by their privacy policies and is not subject to our control.  You acknowledge and agree that once your Personally Identifiable Information is transferred to those third-party vendors, you must contact them directly for all inquiries about the use of your Personally Identifiable Information and their privacy policies. You may request a list of third-party partners or vendors with whom we have shared your Personal Identifiable Information by sending us a request e-mail to: info@business-software.com.

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our traffic patterns and related site information to third-party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

**4\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?**

You may choose not to provide us with your Personal Identifiable Information. In such an event, you can still access and use our Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personally Identifiable Information.

We may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our Company products and services. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, simply let us know by sending us an unsubscribe request to: info@business-software.com. Or, if we provide an op-out option on the e-mail, simple click on it to unsubscribe from our Company e-mail list.

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our site may not work properly in your case.

**5\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**

We have implemented reasonable security procedures intended to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unauthorized disclosure of or access to your Personally Identifiable Information reasonably appropriate to the level of the data concerned.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

**6\. Do we use “cookies”?**

When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly in that case.

We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We will not provide any third-party ad server with any of your Personally Identifiable Information or information about your purchases, if provided by Site. We and our third party ad server will collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad. Other advertisers may also place banner ads on our site in the same manner as above, but we will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to them.

**7\. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third-party sites accessible from our site?**

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites that may be accessible through our Site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult third party site’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other third parties which place advertising on our Site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

**8\. What else should you know about your privacy online?**

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site.  Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors that are under 18 years of age.

If we allow you to set up an account with user name and password, you may update your information or cancel your account at any time.  You may also request to have your Personal Identifiable Information deleted from our database upon request; however, once your Personal Identifiable Information is shared with third-party vendors and you have been contacted by those vendors, you must contact them directly.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, your dealings with this Site, or your Personally Identifiable Information, please send us e-mail to: info@business-software.com.

**9\. What about updates and changes to Privacy Policy?**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you.  Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.

Privacy Policy Last Updated: May 20, 2019.
